<?xml version="1.0"?>


<document>
  <body>
		<p>
		The Salomon project uses the
		<a href="http://subversion.tigris.org/">Subversion</a> version control
		system.  If you're new to Subversion, you can check out the
		<a href="http://svnbook.red-bean.com/">online book</a> about Subversion.
		Note that we are currently using Subversion 1.1.x (there are separate
		versions of the book covering 1.0 and 1.1).
		</p>
		
		<section name="Web Access to Subversion">
			<p>
			If you just want to browse the source code, you can use the
			<a href="http://salomon.iisg.agh.edu.pl/websvn">SVN View
			web interface</a> to Subversion.  This is current at all times.
			</p>
		</section>
        <section name="Normal Subversion Access">
            <P> TO 
            <p>URL to Salomons repository  is: "svn+ssh://salomon.iisg.agh.edu.pl/home/svn/salomon/platform/trunk"</p>
            <ul>
                <li>
                    <h5>Console SVN: </h5>
                    <p>if you have console svn client and you are familiar with cvs then there's nothing new for you here, just type the command: <br/>
                        <div class="source"><pre>
                        svn co svn+ssh://salomon.iisg.agh.edu.pl/home/svn/salomon/platform/trunk -q --username [USERNAME]
                        </pre></div>
                        [USERNAME] is four account name <br/>            
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <h5>GUI SVN client: </h5>
                    <p>Come ON, There are many gui svn clients, I'm sure you can figure out how they work by your self or you don't need the source anyway, You have been given the URL for the repository and that's all you need ;P</p>
                </li>
            </ul>
			<subsection name="Check out from Subversion">
				<p>As shown above</p>
			</subsection>
			<subsection name="Commit Changes to Subversion">
                <p>After you have downloaded the repository and made some (considerable and senseful) changes in it, 
                    its time to commit it back to the repository, the best way to do it is to type: <br/>
                    
                <div class="source"><pre>
                        svn commit
                </pre></div>
                    
                    in the directory of the source code, svn will check which files did you change and send them to the repository, but before you do that make sure that the source that you want to commit is compilable and there are no silly printouts or comments in it. You will be prompted for comment about your commit, write something about what you have changed (not to long ... just somethin meaningful like, "changed this , fixed that", this sort of stuff)
                </p>
			</subsection>
		</section>
		<section name="Building Salomon from Source">
			<p>Refer to the 
			<a href="http://salomon.iisg.agh.edu.pl/twiki/bin/view.cgi/Main/Procedures#Build_Procedure">
			Wiki page</a> for the build procedure.</p>
		</section>
  </body>
</document>
